<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Updates Feed</title><link>https://dark-ro.com/forum/rss/2-updates-feed.xml/</link><description>RSS Feed for Updates</description><language>en</language><item><title>January 28, 2020  - C-3PO's Maintenance Notes</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5955-january-28-2020-c-3pos-maintenance-notes/?do=findComment&comment=32311]]></link><description><![CDATA[Attention citizens of the republic!
 


	 
 


	The scheduled maintenance was a success and the server's start sequence was completed without any issues. DarkRO Rebirth is now running at a self-sustained state and you should be able to perform your normal routines immediately after patching your client.
 


	 
 


	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Turned the lhz_dun03 map PK setting to OFF.
	
	
		Turned the thana_boss map PK setting to OFF.
	
	
		Improved and cleaned the Universal Item ID line in all items.
	
	
		Completely removed the Box of Sunlight's effects.
	
	
		All Color LHZ Auras (Mid &amp; Lower) now have All Stats +1 
		Note: Revert to normal item to automatically convert to costume.
	
	
		All Color Rune of Power (Mid &amp; Lower) now have All Stats +1 
		Note: Revert to normal item to automatically convert to costume.
	
	
		Revamped (Buff) LHZ Cards - Added effects to promote constant usage. 
		BETA RELEASE - These cards will receive constant changes based on the server's meta.
		
			
				High Wizard Card
				
					
						Int +4
					
					
						Attack and magic attack -20%
					
					
						Enables the wearer to see hidden enemies
					
					
						[High Wizard Class]
						
							
								Increases magic attack by 1% for every 10 base Int of the wearer
							
							
								If the user has mastered Gravitational Field at level 5, grants magic attack +10
							
							
								If the user has mastered Soul Drain at level 10, magic attack +2%
							
						
					
				
			
			
				High Priest Card
				
					
						Max SP +5%
					
					
						Has a 5% chance of auto-casting level 4 Safety Wall while being physically attacked
					
					
						Grants 15% resistance against Holy and Dark property attacks
					
					
						[High Priest Class]
						
							
								Increases magic attack by 1% for every 25 base Int of the wearer
							
							
								If the user has mastered Basilica at level 5, increases resistance against all non-Neutral property attacks by 5%
							
							
								If the user has mastered Safety Wall at level 10, auto-casts level 5 Safety Wall instead
							
						
					
				
			
			
				Sniper Card
				
					
						Hit Rate +200
					
					
						Increases ranged damage by 5%. Further increases ranged damage by 1% per refine rate of the weapon
					
					
						Has a 5% chance of healing 15% of the damage dealt as HP
					
					
						[Sniper Class]
						
							
								Increases Hit Rate by 5 for every 25 base Dex of the wearer
							
							
								Increases the chance of healing by 5%
							
							
								If the user has mastered Beast Bane at level 10, further increases ranged damage by 1% per 2 refine of the weapon
							
						
					
				
			
			
				Lord Knight Card
				
					
						Str +3
					
					
						Max HP -25%
					
					
						Enables the use of level 1 Berserk
					
					
						[Lord Knight Class]
						
							
								Increases attack by 5 for every 50 base Str of the wearer
							
							
								If the user has mastered Two-handed Sword Mastery at level 10, grants an additional Str +2 and attack +10
							
							
								If the user has mastered Spear Mastery at level 10, hit +50 and increases ranged damage by 5%
							
						
					
				
			
			
				Whitesmith Card
				
					
						Makes the weapon Unbreakable
					
					
						Increases attack by 5 per refine rate of the weapon
					
					
						Has a chance of auto-casting level 6 Mammonite and level 1 Maximum Over-Thrust while physically attacking
					
					
						[Whitesmith Class]
					
					
						Attack +10%, increases attack by 2 for every 10 base Str of the wearer
						
							
								Has a 3% chance to break the target's weapon and armor while physically attacking
							
							
								Has a 1% chance to break the target's shield and headgear while physically attacking
							
							
								If the wearer has mastered Mammonite at level 10, auto-casts level 10 Mammonite instead, and the Mammonite skill costs 0 zeny
							
						
					
				
			
			
				Assassin Cross Card
				
					
						Crit +15
					
					
						Increases critical damage by 2% per refine rate of the weapon
					
					
						Has a chance of auto-casting level 1 Enchant Deadly Poison while physically attacking and while being physically attacked
					
					
						[Assassin Class]
						
							
								Increases critical damage by 2% for every 20 base Agi of the wearer
							
							
								If the wearer has mastered Enchant Deadly Poison at level 5, increases attack by 5%
							
							
								If the wearer has mastered Soul Destroyer at level 10, reduces after-cast delay of all skills by 15%
							
						
					
				
			
		
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Fixed the Ninja's Clothing Dye Issue
	
	
		Fixed the Gunslinger Clothing Dye Issue
	
	
		Fixed the stacking issue of the 'Recruit Siege Supply Box'. This reverted after an update.
	
	
		Added several fixes to the Card Removal NPC (Old Woman).
	
	
		Fixed the player reported Twin Pom Santa Hat issue where the script was still working despite it being a costume.
	
	
		Fixed the Geiravor's VH issue where the CritRate does not increase from each refine.
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Added the VH Upgrade Quest in @guide.
	
	
		Build Profiles - Released a new NPC for saving and loading Stats and Skills. Located inside Prontera Library.
	
	
		Added the @miningcd command to check Mining Cooldown without entering the map.
	
	
		Released Tier 2 Valkyrie Manteau + Quest (Located near the Tier Upgrade NPC)
		
			
				[Mage, Archer, Thief, Sith &amp; Ninja]
				
					
						Increase perfect dodge by 8 + (refine * 3)
					
					
						If refined to +8, additional perfect dodge +2, and reduces incoming non-Neutral damage by 3%
					
				
			
			
				[Swordsman, Merchant, Acolyte, Jedi &amp; Gunslinger]
				
					
						Reflect 8 + (refine * 3)% melee damage back to enemies
					
					
						If refined to +8, additional 2% melee damage reflect, and reflects 5% of ranged damage back to enemies.
					
				
			
		
	
	
		Rotated Headgears (Add + Remove)
		
			
				Donation Manager
				
					
						Exclusive Donation
						
							
								Blue Electric Aura (Mid &amp; Lower)
							
							
								Red Electric Aura (Mid &amp; Lower)
							
						
					
					
						Bonus Points
						
							
								Red Seraph Wing
							
							
								Mario Hat
							
							
								Love Cheeks
							
							
								Warm Cat Muffler
							
							
								Mafia Dog
							
							
								Sweet Bonnet
							
							
								Nettie Heart Bubblegum
							
						
					
					
						Exclusive Bonus Points
						
							
								Gold Magestic Goat
							
							
								Neptune Helm
							
							
								Black Rune of Power
							
							
								Costume Picnic Basket
							
							
								Eleanor Wig
							
						
					
				
			
			
				Activity Points
				
					
						Aquarius Crown
					
					
						Yellow Baseball Cap
					
					
						Earth Goddess Flower
					
					
						Bloody Butterfly Ears
					
					
						Weisswurst
					
				
			
			
				Vote Points
				
					
						Love Dad Bandana
					
					
						Pink Beanie
					
					
						Crimson Ribbon
					
					
						Tinker Bell Ears
					
					
						Spare Card
					
				
			
			
				KoE
				
					
						Sword Backpack
					
					
						Creed Helm
					
					
						Yaepjyak
					
					
						Benevolent Guardian
					
					
						Emoticon Cute
					
				
			
			
				WoE
				
					
						Umbrella Backpack
					
					
						Garuda Hat
					
					
						Dwarf Beard
					
					
						I love china
					
					
						Emoticon Dead
					
				
			
			
				PvP
				
					
						Rainbow Cloud
					
					
						Rage of Luster
					
					
						Aquarius Diadem
					
					
						Pig Nose
					
					
						Steering Wheel Backpack
					
				
			
		
	



	 
 


	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Updated the Item Database in the website. This is in support of the clickable Universal Item ID System.
	



	 
 


	It is strongly recommended that you update your DarkRO Rebirth Client often to avoid any errors and inconveniences in-game. Please download the latest client on our Website's Downloads Page.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 21:22:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>January 14, 2021  - C-3PO's Maintenance Notes</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5886-january-14-2021-c-3pos-maintenance-notes/?do=findComment&comment=32051]]></link><description><![CDATA[Attention citizens of the republic!
 


	 
 


	The scheduled maintenance was a success and the server's start sequence was completed without any issues. DarkRO Rebirth is now running at a self-sustained state and you should be able to perform your normal routines immediately after patching your client.
 


	 
 


	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Updated Gepard cheat detections.
	
	
		Disabled Mail Service (RodEx)
	
	
		Revamped MVP Cards
		
			
				Berzebub Card
				
					
						
							Reduces casting time by 30%
						 
					
					
						
							INT +3
						 
					
				
			
			
				Boss Ygnizem Card
				
					
						
							Every second, you recover ([base level*2]) HP and ([job level/10]) SP
						 
					
					
						
							Increases Maximum HP and Maximum SP by 12%
						 
					
					
						
							Maximum HP and Maximum SP by +1% per refine rate of the Footgear
						 
					
				
			
			
				Drake Card
				
					
						
							Atk +5%
						 
					
					
						
							Atk +3% per 2 refine rate of the Weapon
						 
					
					
						
							Nullify reduction in damage inflicted on enemies resulting from enemy's size
						 
					
				
			
			
				Kiel-D-01 Card
				
					
						Reduces all skill's after-cast delay by 25%
					
					
						Increases SP cost of all skills by 25%
					
				
			
			
				Orc Hero Card
				
					
						
							Gain immunity to the Stun status
						 
					
					
						
							VIT +3
						 
					
					
						
							If the headgear is refined to +7 or higher, further increases VIT +1 and Max HP +1%
						 
					
					
						
							If the headgear is refined to +9 or higher, further increases VIT +1 and Max HP +1%
						 
					
				
			
			
				
					Garm Card
				 

				
					
						
							Increases physical and magical damage against Water property targets by 1% per refine rate of the Armor
						 
					
					
						
							Add a 50% chance of auto casting 'Freeze' on an enemy when the user receives Physical Damage
						 

						
							
								
									[ Garm Baby Card Combo ]
								 
							
							
								
									Atk and MAtk +5 per refine rate of the weapon
								 
							
							
								
									Further increases physical and magical damage against Water property targets by 1% per 2 refine rate of the weapon
								 
							
						
					
				
			
			
				
					Ktullanux Card
				 

				
					
						
							Increases damage against Fire Property monsters by 50%
						 
					
					
						
							Add a 5% chance of auto casting Level 10 Frost Nova on an enemy when the user receives Physical Damage
						 
					
					
						
							Increases the damage of Cold Bolt, Frost Diver, Frost Nova, Freezing Spear, and Storm Gust by 5%
						 

						
							
								
									[ Stormy Knight Card ]
								 
							
							
								
									Increases the damage of Cold Bolt, Frost Diver, Frost Nova, Freezing Spear, and Storm Gust by 1% per 3 refine rate of the Weapon
								 
							
						
					
				
			
			
				
					Stormy Knight Card
				 

				
					
						
							Atk +1% per refine rate of the Weapon
						 
					
					
						
							MAtk +1% per 3 refine rate of the Weapon
						 
					
					
						
							Add a 2% chance of auto casting Level 2 Storm Gust on the enemy when attacking. If worn by Mage, Acolyte, or Ninja classes, instead casts level 5 Storm Gust
						 
					
					
						
							Has 25% chance of Freezing an enemy when attacking
						 
					
				
			
		
	
	
		Revamped Tier 2 Items
		
			
				Valkyrie Helm
				
					
						DEX +7
					
					
						STR +7
					
					
						Reduce Damage from Demi-Humans by 10%
					
					
						Receive 10% more Damage from Shadow attacks
					
					
						Reduce After-Cast Delay by 5%
					
					
						If worn with Tier 2 Valkyrie Armor grants Str +1 and Vit +1
					
					
						If worn with Tier 2 Valkyrie Manteau grants Int +1 and Dex +1
					
					
						If worn with Tier 2 Valkyrie Shoes grants Agi +1 and Luk +1
					
				
			
			
				Valkyrie Armor
				
					
						All Stats +1
					
					
						Immune to Freeze
					
					
						Indestructible
					
					
						[Mage, Archer, Acolyte, Sith, Ninja]
						
							
								50% Resistance to Silence
							
						
					
					
						[Swordsman, Merchant, Thief, Jedi, Gunslinger]
						
							
								50% Resistance to Stun
							
						
					
					
						Max HP &amp; SP +3%
					
					
						ATK + 2%
					
					
						MATK +2%
					
				
			
			
				Valkyrie Shield
				
					
						MDEF +10
					
					
						Immune to Stone Curse
					
					
						Indestructible
					
					
						Reduce Damage from Water, Fire, Undead &amp; Shadow by 25%.
					
					
						Reduce Damage from Earth, Wind &amp; Holy by 5%.
					
					
						Reflect +5%
					
				
			
			
				Valkyrie Shoes
				
					
						Immune to Sleep
					
					
						Movement Speed +10%
					
					
						Indestructible
					
					
						MaxHP &amp; MaxSP + 7.5%
					
					
						[Mage, Archer, Acolyte, Sith &amp; Ninja]
						
							
								MaxHP + 2.5%; additional MaxHP + [1 * (BaseLVL / 10)]%
							
						
					
					
						[Swordsman, Merchant, Thief, Jedi &amp; Gunslinger]
						
							
								MaxSP + 2.5%; additional MaxSP + [1 * (JobLVL / 10)]%
							
						
					
				
			
			
				Nile Rose
				
					
						All Stats +5
					
					
						ATK &amp; MATK +2%
					
				
			
			
				Kakashi's Head Protector
				
					
						DEX +20
					
					
						Dramatically Increases Movement Speed
					
					
						Receive -50% DMG from Fire
					
					
						Receive +25% DMG from Water
					
					
						Increase Range DMG by +8%
					
				
			
			
				Traveler's Hat
				
					
						LUK +12
					
					
						AGI +4
					
					
						STR +5
					
					
						CRIT Rate +15
					
					
						CRIT Damage +9%
					
				
			
		
	
	
		Fixed the Streamer Megaphone Cooldown issue.
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Fixed the Garment Wing Issue on Jedi, Sith and Padawan Classes.
	
	
		Fixed the Jejecap Regeneration Effect.
	
	
		Fixed the Aurodium Set Effects
	
	
		Fixed the Aurodium Set Items where they cannot be equipped by Sith, Jedi and Padawan classes.
	
	
		Updated Chain of Commandments headgear location.
	
	
		Fixed the Guild Hall Punching Bag issue where Siths clone them and cause errors.
	
	
		Fixed the Baby Penguin headgear description.
	
	
		Fixed the Deviruchi Headphones' automatic costume status.
	
	
		Fixed the Twin Pom Pom's automatic costume status.
	



	 
 


	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Lowered the WoE: SE Guardian Stone HP from 40m down to 10m.
	
	
		Lowered the WoE: SE Barricade HP from 20m down to 5m.
	
	
		Increased the WoE: SE Guardian Stone Repair Cooldown from 5 minutes to 15 minutes.
	
	
		Disabled Yggdrasil Leaf in Training Ground (@go 15)
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Updated Website 
		The website is not 100% complete but all essential functions are working. Some content will still be placeholders and will be updated as we go without prior notice. Please report any issues so we can fix them ASAP.
	
	
		Game Server Host Move 
		The server is now located in Germany but the old host location in Hong Kong has not been deactivated in case we need to move back. Our initial tests seem to be fine so we're moving on to live testing with full player base.
	



	 
 


	It is strongly recommended that you update your DarkRO Rebirth Client often to avoid any errors and inconveniences in-game. Please download the latest client on our Website's Downloads Page.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 22:05:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>December 23, 2020  - C-3PO's Maintenance Notes</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5751-december-23-2020-c-3pos-maintenance-notes/?do=findComment&comment=31691]]></link><description>Attention citizens of the republic!
 


	 
 


	The scheduled maintenance was a success and the server's start sequence was completed without any issues. DarkRO Rebirth is now running at a self-sustained state and you should be able to perform your normal routines immediately after patching your client.
 


	 
 


	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Gepard Update
	
	
		Removed a number of headgears from shops
	
	
		Updated the descriptions of Ores from Mining
	
	
		Updated the Mining Guardian monster names
	
	
		Updated the Mining Guardian kill broadcast
	
	
		Allowed the Recruit Siege Supply Box to stack
	
	
		Allowed the Diary Magic Powder to be sold to NPCs.
	
	
		Updated the Equipment Option Scroll descriptions.
	
	
		Updated Rose Sheen Aura description
	
	
		Added delay to the @loginrewards command to avoid unnecessary server load.
	
	
		Added a warning to the Costume NPC to avoid wrong item conversions.
	
	
		Added a weight restriction on the Daily Login Rewards to avoid accidental item loss.
	
	
		Rebalanced Force-Imbued Blade
	
	
		Updated Equipment Option NPC Name to The Armorer
	
	
		Updated The Armorer dialogue
	
	
		Fixed Cradossk (Guild Hall Registration) Dialogue
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Fixed the Atomic Energy Combo effect descriptions.
	
	
		Fixed Vending time limit. Now set to unlimited.
	
	
		Fixed the Guild Announcement where it would not save.
	
	
		Fixed the Evolved Whisper Mask item moves.
	
	
		Fixed the WoE SE Treasure Box Issue.
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Changed Prontera Theme - Christmas
	
	
		Guild Hall Updates
		
			
				Guest Access (Level 4) is now working
			
			
				Punching Bags
			
		
	
	
		Added New Items
		
			
				KoE Shop
				
					
						Diablo Helm
					
					
						Cat Ears Cape
					
					
						Khalitzburg Helm
					
					
						Dokkebi Mask 
					
					
						Whistle
					
				
			
			
				WoE Shop
				
					
						Thanatos Despero Mask
					
					
						Husky Hat
					
					
						UFO Poring Hat
					
					
						Mochiring Hat
					
					
						Shaving Foam
					
				
			
			
				PvP Shop
				
					
						Mask of Ifrit
					
					
						Tongue Charm
					
					
						Scuba Mask
					
					
						Thunderstorm Cloud
					
					
						Little Feather Hat
					
				
			
			
				Activity Shop
				
					
						Republic Hat
					
					
						Poster Girl Hat
					
					
						Dolor Thanatos Drooping
					
					
						YinYang Earrings
					
					
						Sugared Fruit Stick
					
				
			
			
				Vote Shop
				
					
						Crown of Strawberry Prince
					
					
						Thorny Hairband
					
					
						Chain of Commandments
					
					
						Dragonfly Monocle
					
					
						Scissorhand Model
					
				
			
			
				Donation Bonus
				
					
						Gram Peony
					
					
						Cat Ears Hat
					
					
						Crow Tengu
					
					
						Snownow Hat
					
					
						Baby Penguin
					
					
						Chilly Breath
					
					
						Snowman Hat
					
				
			
			
				Exclusive Bonus
				
					
						Akatsuki Hat
					
					
						Christmas Box
					
					
						Light Thunderstroke
					
					
						Dark Thunderstroke
					
				
			
		
	
	
		Added New Valkyrie Helm Variants
		
			
				Sanngrior's Valkyrie Helm (Red)
			
			
				Kara's Valkyrie Helm (Black)
			
			
				Herja's Valkyrie Helm (Venom)
			
			
				Geiravor's Valkyrie Helm (Geo)
			
			
				Eir's Valkyrie Helm (Mystic)
			
		
	
	
		Added New VH Variant Quest. (Somewhere in Sky Garden)
	



	 
 


	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Password Reset on the website is now fixed.
	



	 
 


	It is strongly recommended that you update your DarkRO Rebirth Client often to avoid any errors and inconveniences in-game. Please download the latest client on our Website's Downloads Page.</description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 23:25:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>December 1, 2020  - C-3PO's Maintenance Notes</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5642-december-1-2020-c-3pos-maintenance-notes/?do=findComment&comment=31223]]></link><description><![CDATA[Attention citizens of the republic!
 


	 
 


	The scheduled maintenance was a success and the server's start sequence was completed without any issues. DarkRO Rebirth is now running at a self-sustained state and you should be able to perform your normal routines immediately after patching your client.
 


	 
 


	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Guild Hall Update
		
			
				Removed all existing Guild Turfs
			
			
				All existing Guild Halls will be reset.
			
			
				Added New Pricing Packages. (Please check Cradossk before finalizing your registration)
			
			
				IMPORTANT NOTE: The Leader Password is an additional security measure when interacting with Jah Zapar (Guest Access NPC). Only your Guild Master should know this.
			
			
				Future Update: Special WoE Warper, Training Dummy, Guest Access
			
		
	
	
		Removed graymap.grf
	
	
		Added proper labels to Star Wars Box items.
	
	
		Pets re-enabled in Towns
	
	
		Dark &amp; Light Thunderstroke are now automatically Costumes.
	
	
		Disabled @warp when in the Training Grounds map.
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Fixed Force-Imbued Blade where it gives gives extra INT. ATK also fixed.
	
	
		Fixed Kamen Rider Helm Slot
	
	
		Fixed Kamen Rider Helm Script
	
	
		Fixed Hollow Mask 2.0 Slot
	
	
		Fixed DB and BB restriction in several maps.
	
	
		Fixed level requirement in Training Grounds (@go 15)
	
	
		Fixed Talisman Descriptions.
	
	
		Fixed Assassin Cross Card multiplier script error.
	
	
		Removed item restrictions from guild_vs maps.
	
	
		Fixed Zed's Staff error from the THQ.
	
	
		Fixed Izlude Town non-walkable cells.
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Daily Login Rewards System
		
			
				@loginrewards - Checks your claim status.
			
			
				@loginrewards claim - Claims your Daily Login Reward.
			
			
				Restricted to 1 per MAC.
			
		
	
	
		Equipment Option System - Adds a separate stat bonus to your equipment.
		
			
				The Armorer is located in Einbech. Use @guide to find her.
			
			
				Upper HG - HP and SP Bonuses
			
			
				Armor - Stat Bonuses
			
			
				Shield - Race Bonuses
			
			
				Garment - Property Bonuses
			
			
				Footgear - Damage Bonuses
			
			
				Requires a special Equipment Option Scroll obtainable from Monster Arena, Mining, Mine Guardian, Events, etc.
			
		
	
	
		Mining System - 2 Week Promo/Beta Release! - Still being polished. 
		Mine for Ores that can be used for different quests and excited rewards!
		
			
				A complete guide will be posted soon. For now, the Mining NPCs around the stone locations can explain the mechanics.
			
			
				Entrance Quest is waived for the first 2 weeks but requires 20 Credits per warp.
			
			
				How to get there - Find Karam Pucci in Alberta. Use @guide to find him.
			
			
				Other Restrictions
				
					
						Uses 1 Old Pick (7318) per attempt.
					
					
						Must be 255/100
					
					
						Must wear Safety Helm (5009) or Mine Hat (5031)
					
					
						Must wear Safety Boots (2413) - Dropped by RSX 0806
					
					
						Must wear 2pcs Safety Rings (2615)
					
					
						Can only use the Rock Ridge Fly Wing.
					
					
						PK  is Off.
					
				
			
			
				Miner Rank &amp; Stones
				
					
						Lv. 0: Candidate (Thorilide)
					
					
						Lv. 1: Rookie (Agrocite)
					
					
						Lv. 2: Apprentice (Beskar)
					
					
						Lv. 3: Worker (Kallistan Gem)
					
					
						Lv. 4: Pitman (Firkrann Crystal)
					
					
						Lv. 5: Expert (Eraladium)
					
					
						Lv. 6: Craftsman (Mirkanite)
					
					
						Lv. 7: Master (Sun Crystal + Corusca Gem)
					
				
			
		
	
	
		New Headgear Rotation
		
			
				Exclusive Donation
				
					
						Red Force Aura (L&amp;M)
					
					
						Cyan Force Aura (L&amp;M)
					
				
			
			
				Exclusive Donation Bonus
				
					
						Amidamaru Spirit (M)
					
					
						Blade of Dragon (M)
					
					
						Ruby Thunderstroke(L)
					
					
						Mystic Thunderstroke(L)
					
					
						Naruto Hairband
					
				
			
			
				Donation Bonus
				
					
						Flying Galapago
					
					
						Magical Feather
					
					
						Glasses Without Lens
					
					
						Goldfish Sun Hat
					
					
						Blue Eremes Scarf
					
					
						Smoking Pipe
					
				
			
			
				Activity Shop
				
					
						Anemos Mask
					
					
						Foxtail in Mouth
					
					
						Monochrome Cap
					
					
						Sakura Hairband
					
					
						Long Wolf Ears
					
				
			
			
				Vote Shop
				
					
						Misty Ears
					
					
						Black Devil Mask
					
					
						Leopard Ear Hat
					
					
						Cherry Twig in Mouth
					
					
						Yellow Ribbon Hairband
					
				
			
		
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Removed Agit Lords Script
	
	
		Added back previous WoE Rank NPC in Prontera
	
	
		Reduced Guardian Stone HP from 60m to 45m
	
	
		Reduced Barricade HP from 40m to 30m
	
	
		Battlegrounds Re-Release on BETA - Observation will continue in the Live Server.
	



	 
 


	 
 


	It is strongly recommended that you update your DarkRO Rebirth Client often to avoid any errors and inconveniences in-game. Please download the latest client on our Website's Downloads Page.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 23:58:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>November 13, 2020  - C-3PO's Maintenance Notes</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5565-november-13-2020-c-3pos-maintenance-notes/?do=findComment&comment=30842]]></link><description>Attention citizens of the republic!
 


	 
 


	The scheduled maintenance was a success and the server's start sequence was completed without any issues. DarkRO Rebirth is now running at a self-sustained state and you should be able to perform your normal routines immediately after patching your client.
 


	 
 


	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Restored normal permanent mapflags in nif_fild01.
	
	
		Moved the @guide images to the center of the screen.
	
	
		Improved Ifrit Card description to prevent confusion.
	
	
		Removed some headgears from WoE Shop, KoE Shop and PvP Shop.
	
	
		Added new headgears
		
			
				PvP Shop
				
					
						Lude Mask
					
					
						Happy Poop Hat
					
					
						Silk Hat of Earth
					
					
						Queen Anne's Revenge
					
					
						Flower Pot Mask
					
				
			
			
				WoE Shop
				
					
						Emoticon Pif
					
					
						Campus Festival
					
					
						Lupus Hair
					
					
						White Tomboy Fairy Ears
					
					
						White Rogue Cape
					
				
			
			
				KoE Shop
				
					
						Emoticon Slur
					
					
						Protect Feathers
					
					
						Hunting Cap of Gust
					
					
						Panda Hoody
					
					
						King Poring Hat
					
				
			
		
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Fixed WoE Points where it would keep giving points on every portal.
	
	
		Fixed Dragon Wings Upgrade dialogue.
	
	
		Fixed Halter Lead bug where it would become permanent after expiration and disallows you from performing certain actions.
	
	
		Fixed Geo Dragon Wing's lacking 5 LUK stat.
	
	
		Fixed the comma in @whosell prices.
	
	
		Removed the +1 stat from Kirin Wings.
	
	
		Fixed Halloween Hat Name
	
	
		Fixed the Kamen Rider Helm script.
	
	
		Renamed one of the Hallow Masks to Hallow Mask 2.0.
	
	
		Fixed Hallow Mask script.
	
	
		Added back slots to Hollow Mask, Hollow Mask 2.0 and Kamen Rider Helm.
	
	
		Fixed Icarus Spear description where it displayed the wrong weight value.
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Added Watto in Morocc that offers event prizes. Items not yet available, NPC hidden temporarily.
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Fixed pvp announcement and @listenpk function.
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
		Updated all files in Downloads Page last November 3, 2020.
	



	 
 


	It is strongly recommended that you update your DarkRO Rebirth Client often to avoid any errors and inconveniences in-game. Please download the latest client on our Website's Downloads Page.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 20:33:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>