<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Events Feed</title><link>https://dark-ro.com/forum/rss/3-events-feed.xml/</link><description>RSS Feed for Events</description><language>en</language><item><title>[FORUM EVENT] New Player Guide Event</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5882-forum-event-new-player-guide-event/?do=findComment&comment=32045]]></link><description>OVERVIEW
 


	 
 


	Greetings Dark RO Rebirth Players!
 


	 
 


	We want to give the best experience to our new players and those that are just starting their Journey in our server. From Obi Wan interview until their first WOE experience, we would like to ask from you, the veteran players, what is the fastest way to get complete WOE equipment or meet the minimum guild requirements. The top 3 guides will be posted in the home page of the dark-ro.com website and will receive prizes. You never know you might just meet the chosen one who will bring balance back to the Force.
 


	 
 


	Mechanics
 


	
		
			Submit your guide below, reply to this topic.
		 
	
	
		
			Make a written guide from Obi-wan Interview, to leveling, to buying the basic farming equipment, to mid-tier farming techniques and to getting the minimum requirements to join WOE.
		 
	
	
		
			Under the comments section of this forum post you need to reply, you need to have a well written guide that is understandable (English only).
		 
	
	
		
			Use computations in terms of how many Credits a player can profit per hour. The guide needs to be time-bound so new players know how much time they need to grind.
		 
	
	
		
			You can showcase any form of farming technique: Refining, Buy and Sell, DB/BB, ET, MA etc.
		 
	



	
		
			Please submit your guides between Jan 18 to Feb 1.
		 
	
	
		
			GMs will judge the guides from from Feb 2 to Feb 9.
		 
	
	
		
			We will be announcing the winners on Feb 13.
		 
	



	 
 


	Criterias for Winning
 


	
		
			GM Team will judge the guides and show the computation for the winners
		 

		
			
				
					25% Flow of the Guide
				 
			
			
				
					25% Easy to Learn
				 
			
			
				
					25% Fun and Engaging
				 
			
			
				
					25% Speed to get basic WOE Equipment (VA Tier 1 and Vshield Tier 1+GTB)
				 
			
		
	



	 
 


	Format for Submission
 


	Needs to contain the following details
 


	
		
			IGN
		 
	
	
		
			Full Name
		 
	
	
		
			Facebook Link
		 
	
	
		
			Star Wars Quote
		 
	
	
		
			Guide
		 

		
			
				
					Obi Wan Answers
				 
			
			
				
					First Job to take
				 
			
			
				
					Leveling and Stats
				 
			
			
				
					Newbie Farming (Fancy Set)
				 
			
			
				
					Mid-Tier Farming (With Decent Farmed Equipment)
				 
			
			
				
					Computation: Road to Valkyrie Armor Tier 1 (18B) + Valkyrie Shield w/GTB (16B)
				 

				
					
						
							Must show how many hours needed
						 
					
				
			
		
	



	 
 


	PRIZE
 


	1st Prize: 300 Black Credits + Custom Cap (https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/4693-the-cap-forge-create-your-custom-cap/?tab=comments#comment-26678)
 


	 
 


	2nd Prize: 200 Black Credits
 


	 
 


	3rd Prize: 100B Black Credits
 


	 
 


	Consolation based on GM evaluation: 5x Black Credits
 


	 
 


	&#x201C;The Force Is Strong With This One&#x201D; - Darth Vader</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 18:06:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AGIT LORDS - SEASON 3</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5875-agit-lords-season-3/?do=findComment&comment=32018]]></link><description>Be the Lords of DarkRO! Prove the might of your Guild once and for all and let your teamwork do the talking!
 


	May the force be with you all!
 


	 
 


	Season 3 of DarkRO: Rebirth's Agit Lords will start on January 23, 2020!
 


	 
 


	OVERVIEW
 


	The time has come again to prove who are the real Kings of DarkRO Rebirth. Ready your guild and defeat all that stand in your way. This Event shall be known as DarkRO: Rebirth's Agit Lords Season 3, or AL3. It will be comprised of 2 events, Agit Lords and Dark Tournament.
 


	 
 


	 
 


	Event 1: Agit Lords
 


	
		
			Starts on January 23, 2021.
		 
	
	
		
			Ends on Feb 11, 2021.
		 
	
	
		
			We will be using the AGIT HOLDER POINT SYSTEM. Each Castle will have a certain corresponding point depending on the date (3,2,1,0). Castles with points will be reduced in the later parts of the Agit Lords phase to encourage guilds to be more competitive. Rotation of points per castle will also vary based on the date.
		 
	
	
		
			Points will only be given during Thursday, Saturday Night and Sunday WoE slots.
		 
	
	
		
			Top 12 will be invited to The Dark Tournament. In the event of a tie in the 12th place, we will assign a castle on the last day for those tied. The holder of that castle will be the 12th place in the Agit Lords.
		 
	
	
		
			Second Guilds
		 

		
			
				
					They will be allowed. Friendly fire enabled (Guild Alliance issue fixed, GUILD ALLAINCE WILL NOT WORK IN AGIT LORDS).
				 
			
			
				
					Points earned by the Second Guild will not be added to the main guild.
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			The same restrictions with the usual WoE applies (MBK/Provoke/Ice Wall/Ensemble/LHZ Cards).
		 
	
	
		
			Pets are not allowed inside the castle grounds.
		 
	
	
		
			SE WOE every Tuesday and Saturday MORNING WOE will still be open for regular WOE during Agit Lords but they will not give points.
		 
	



	 
 


	 
 


	Event 2: The Dark Tournament (Guild VS Guild)
 


	
		
			Lottery to determine Group A and B will be on Feb 11 after the last WOE.
		 
	
	
		
			Will be divided into 2 parts Group Stage and Playoffs
		 
	
	
		
			Group Stage
		 

		
			
				
					Round Robin. Teams will be divided into 2 groups, 6 guilds each. Teams will fight their fellow Groupmates once. Total of 5 games each Guild for the Group Stage.
				 
			
			
				
					Saturday, Feb 13, 2021 - 9:00PM (GMT+8) (WOE will be moved to 7pm-8pm)
				 
			
			
				
					Sunday, Feb 14, 2021 - 9:00PM (GMT+8) (WOE will be moved to 7pm-8pm)
				 
			
			
				
					Thursday, Feb 18, 2021 - 9:00PM (GMT+8) (WOE will be moved to 7pm-8pm)
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Playoffs
		 

		
			
				
					Saturday, Feb 20, 2021 - 9:00PM (GMT+8) (WOE will be moved to 7pm-8pm)
				 
			
			
				
					Sunday, Feb 21, 2021 - 9:00PM (GMT+8) (WOE will be moved to 7pm-8pm)
				 
			
			
				
					Thursday, Feb 25, 2021 - 9:00PM (GMT+8) (WOE will be moved to 7pm-8pm)
				 
			
			
				
					Finals - Saturday, Feb 27, 2021 - 9:00PM (GMT+8) (WOE will be moved to 7pm-8pm)
				 
			
		
	



	 
 


	 
 


	Agit Lords Schedule
 


	
		
			Jan 23 Saturday (9PM - 10PM Server time)
		 

		
			
				
					Repherion +3
				 
			
			
				
					Nuemberg +2
				 
			
			
				
					Sacred Altar +1
				 
			
			
				
					Bamboo Grove Hill +1
				 
			
			
				
					Skoegul +1
				 
			
			
				
					Gondul +1
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Jan 24 Sunday (9PM - 10PM Server time)
		 

		
			
				
					Bright Arbor +3
				 
			
			
				
					Kriemhild +2
				 
			
			
				
					Swanhild +1
				 
			
			
				
					Fadhgridh +1
				 
			
			
				
					Bergel +1
				 
			
			
				
					Mersetzdeitz +1
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Jan 28 Thursday (9PM - 10PM Server time)
		 

		
			
				
					Neuschwanstein +1
				 
			
			
				
					Hohenschwangau +1
				 
			
			
				
					Eeyolbriggar +3
				 
			
			
				
					Yesnelph +2
				 
			
			
				
					Scarlet Palace +1
				 
			
			
				
					Holy Shadow +1
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Jan 30 Saturday (9PM - 10PM Server time) - minus 2 castles
		 

		
			
				
					Repherion +1
				 
			
			
				
					Nuemberg +0
				 
			
			
				
					Sacred Altar +3
				 
			
			
				
					Bamboo Grove Hill +2
				 
			
			
				
					Skoegul +1
				 
			
			
				
					Gondul +1
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Jan 31 Sunday (9PM - 10PM Server time) 
		 

		
			
				
					Bright Arbor +1
				 
			
			
				
					Kriemhild +0
				 
			
			
				
					Swanhild +3
				 
			
			
				
					Fadhgridh +2
				 
			
			
				
					Bergel +1
				 
			
			
				
					Mersetzdeitz +1
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Feb 4 Thursday (9PM - 10PM Server time)
		 

		
			
				
					Neuschwanstein +1
				 
			
			
				
					Hohenschwangau +1
				 
			
			
				
					Eeyolbriggar +1
				 
			
			
				
					Yesnelph +0
				 
			
			
				
					Scarlet Palace +3
				 
			
			
				
					Holy Shadow +2
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Feb 6 Saturday (9PM - 10PM Server time)
		 

		
			
				
					Repherion +1
				 
			
			
				
					Nuemberg +1
				 
			
			
				
					Sacred Altar +0
				 
			
			
				
					Bamboo Grove Hill +0
				 
			
			
				
					Skoegul +3
				 
			
			
				
					Gondul +2
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Feb 7 Sunday (9PM - 10PM Server time)
		 

		
			
				
					Bright Arbor +1
				 
			
			
				
					Kriemhild +1
				 
			
			
				
					Swanhild +0
				 
			
			
				
					Fadhgridh +0
				 
			
			
				
					Bergel +3
				 
			
			
				
					Mersetzdeitz +2
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Feb 11 Thursday (9PM - 10PM Server time)
		 

		
			
				
					Neuschwanstein +0 (Hot Agit for Tie-Breaker of 12th place)
				 
			
			
				
					Hohenschwangau +0
				 
			
			
				
					Eeyolbriggar +3
				 
			
			
				
					Yesnelph +2
				 
			
			
				
					Scarlet Palace +1
				 
			
			
				
					Holy Shadow +1
				 
			
		
	



	 
 


	 
 


	Second Guilds (Agit Lords)
 


	
		
			They will be allowed. Friendly fire enabled. Guild Alliance disabled.
		 
	
	
		
			Points earned will not be added to the main guild.
		 
	
	
		
			The same restrictions with the usual WoE applies (MBK/Provoke/Ice Wall/Ensemble/LHZ Cards)
		 
	
	
		
			Pets are not allowed inside the castle grounds.
		 
	



	 
 


	Skill Restrictions
 


	The following skill buffs will be removed upon entering the castle grounds:
 


	
		
			Maximum Over Thrust
		 
	
	
		
			Assumptio
		 
	
	
		
			Enchant Deadly Poison
		 
	
	
		
			Berserk
		 
	
	
		
			All ensemble related buffs
		 
	



	 
 


	Skill you can't use inside the guild arena
 


	
		
			Assumptio
		 
	
	
		
			Ice wall
		 
	



	 
 


	 
 


	THE DARK TOURNAMENT: Additional Rules
 


	 
 


	
		
			If there are ties for the last few spots. We will do a best of 1 GVG.
		 
	
	
		
			We will first conduct a Group Stage for the 12 qualified guilds participating in The Dark Tournament. Guilds will be divided into 2 groups (Group A and B), and the guilds in each group will battle against each other (Round Robin, Best of 1). We will play the Group Stage for a total of 3 times, we will call these rounds, in 3 separate days. Each Guild will face the other guilds in the group only once in a best of 1 match. Winner of the match will get 1 POINT.
		 
	
	
		
			Lottery will be conducted on Feb 11 with Streamers and GMs present. Lottery program will pick from Group A 1st pick then Group B first pick, and so on.
		 
	
	
		
			Top 2 of each group will advance to the Double Elimination Main Stage while the Top 3-6 of each group will first fight a best-of-1-Win-or-Go-Home match to advance to the Double Elimination Main Stage.
		 
	
	
		
			Prohibited Cards: LHZ Cards ONLY.
		 
	
	
		
			No armor and weapon prohibitions. Everything, including the newly updated and revamped weapons, will be allowed.
		 
	
	
		
			A test recall will be done. All participating guilds will be recalled one-by-one inside the GvG arena before the war proper to make sure they follow the member requirement.
		 
	
	
		
			Pets, mercenaries, and homunculi are not allowed inside the arena. Violators will be issued a warning. A second violation will incur a disqualification for the current round.
		 
	
	
		
			Guild Masters are not allowed to use the skill Emergency Call inside the arena.
		 
	
	
		
			Each Main Stage match will be a Best of 3, Double Elimination.
		 
	
	
		
			Best of 5 for Lower Bracket Finals and Grand Finals match in the Main Stage.
		 
	
	
		
			Guilds will be given 5 minutes of preparation time.
		 

		
			
				
					GMs will announce the fight and give teams 1 minute before recall.
				 
			
			
				
					Right after recall, doom will be initiated. IMPORTANT: We will not be lenient anymore with guilds who will move outside of their area. We will only give 2 warnings. We will DQ any guild who will not follow this rule. 
				 
			
			
				
					Teams are given 3 minutes to inform the GMs of any members that were not recalled or got DC during recall. As per our rules, only 1 DC call will be entertained regardless of reason. Please create a pub on your side of the GVG map to inform GMs of the request. If second recall is used, GM will automatically use doom right after 2nd recall and Host will shout "No more recall from both Guilds."
				 
			
			
				
					30 seconds will be given to both guilds to rebuff and prepare. Again no DC call will be entertained during this period.
				 
			
			
				
					GMs will not ask if Guilds are ready. We will immediately countdown from 10 to 1 and start GVG. Again, guilds should not be moving unless GMs gave the GO/FIGHT signal.
				 
			
		
	
	
		
			Once the guilds are recalled inside the arena for the match, the event master will then check both sides alternately for disconnection calls. If the guild is ready, the guild master should notify the event master by opening a chatroom or using @request. The event master will only answer to the guild master.
		 
	
	
		
			In case of a disconnection call, the guild will only be allowed a maximum of 3 minutes to wait for their disconnected members.
		 
	
	
		
			Only one disconnection call will be entertained per match. Succeeding disconnection calls will not be entertained. Thus, the guild will have to fight with its current present members.
		 
	
	
		
			No disconnection calls will also be entertained in the middle of the brawl or after the "GO" signal from the event master.
		 
	
	
		
			Both guilds are not to move from their assigned areas until the "GO" signal from the event master is broadcasted. Violating this rule will result in a warning, a third violation will result in a disqualification for the current round.
		 
	
	
		
			Each round will only last for 10 minutes. After the time limit, the event master will disable all skills. Surviving players of both guilds are expected to immediately form a line next to each other. A headcount will be done for the remaining members of both guilds. Whoever has the higher number of surviving members wins the round.
		 
	
	
		
			Guilds that do not show any sign of engagement, eg: waiting for the opponent and not trying to engage or moving away from the approaching opponent/excessive running, within 1 minute during the clash will be given a warning. 2nd warning will incur a point for the opposing guild, then the battle will reset and continue on to the next round.
		 
	
	
		
			We strongly recommend not to use any customized GRFs. We will not be held responsible for any errors that occur and this will not be considered as a disconnection call.
		 
	
	
		
			Any type of 3PP or cheat that will used and caught in the act during the event will be sanctioned. As for the guild, an automatic disqualification, as for the the individual player who cheated, an investigation will be conducted but the account will remain on hold/banned until the investigation is finished.
		 
	
	
		
			Any additional rules will be made and added as necessary.
		 
	



	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	
 


	 
 


	AGIT LORDS PRIZES
 


	Rank 1: 300 USD + 500 Donation Ticket + 300 Black Credits + 42 Event Box + 2pcs Star Wars Box + 2 pcs 4th Job Ticket + 5 Job Ticket
 


	Rank 2: 300 Donation Ticket + 200 Black Credits + 42 Event Boxes + 1pcs Star Wars Box + 1 4th Job Ticket + 3 Job Ticket
 


	Rank 3: 200 Donation Ticket + 100 Black Credits + 42 Event Boxes + 1pcs Star Wars Box + 2 Job Ticket
 


	Rank 4: 80 Black Credits + 42  Event Boxes + 2 4th Job Ticket + 2 Job Ticket
 


	Rank 5: 60 Black Credits + 42 Event Boxes + 2 Job Tickets
 


	Rank 6: 40 Black Credits + 42 Event Boxes + 1 Job Tickets
 


	Rank 7: 20 Black Credits + 42 Event Boxes + 1 Job Tickets
 


	Rank 8-16: 42 Event Boxes + 1 Job Ticket
 


	 
	 
 


	THE DARK TOURNAMENT PRIZES
 


	 
 


	Champion: 750 USD + 500 Donation Ticket + 500 Black Credits + Exclusive Auras + 42 Guild member will receive Guild Custom Cap (Guild Bound)
 


	 
 


	First Runner Up: 300 USD + 300 Donation Ticket + 200 Black Credits + 1 Star Wars Box
 


	 
 


	Second Runner Up: 150 USD + 200 Donation Ticket + 100 Black Credits + 1 Star Wars Box
 


	 
 


	&#x201C;Be careful not to choke on your aspirations.&#x201D; -Darth Vader
 


	 
 


	Note: Rules, Information and Rewards are subject to change without PRIOR NOTICE. Emergency Maintenances may be conducted if necessary due this event being one of the biggest. *The cash prizes may be converted to ROK points at the option of the guild master*</description><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 05:20:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>[FORUM EVENT] DarkRO: Rebirth Loading Screen Contest 2021!</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5869-forum-event-darkro-rebirth-loading-screen-contest-2021/?do=findComment&comment=31989]]></link><description>We would like to invite all the artists of Dark RO Rebirth! Create a DarkRO: Rebirth loading screen with the theme "Star Wars and Ragnarok Related"
 


	 
 


	The Winner will be chosen by popularity vote from FB and GM&#x2019;s Choice.
 


	 
 


	Players need to submit from January 11 to January 30.
 


	On January 30, GMs will compile all entries submitted in the Forums and Discord and post it in 1 album in the Facebook Group
 


	Voting will start from January 31 to February 6.
 


	We will announce the winners by Feb 13.
 


	 
 


	Mechanics: 
 


	 
 


	
		
			Loading screen must be related to DarkRO: Rebirth and Star Wars
		 
	
	
		
			All art must be .jpg format, 1920x1080 Pixel
		 
	
	
		
			Loading screen needs to have DarkRO: Rebirth logo. You can edit the logo to fit your design. Example: Darken the shade or take out white background. 
			 
			
		 
	



	 
 


	You can submit as many as 5 Loading Screens but Strictly only 1 winning artwork will be considered from the owner.
 


	Artworks used in the loading screen needs to be original and must be digitally created, if there is evidence that you stole the artwork from someone else, we will automatically disqualify you from the event.
 


	 
 


	Submitting Loading Screens (Needs to be submitted from January 11 to January 30)
 


	 
 


	               1. IGN:
 


	               2. Full Name:
 


	               3. Facebook Link: ( Legit Facebook. So we can know how we can give you the prize if you're unavailable in-game. )
 


	               4. Caption of Artwork (will be scored)
 


	 
 


	Forums: Should be submitted in this thread with the following Description above
 


	 
 


	Guide to upload Image in Forum: https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5349-screenshot-upload-guide-without-errors/
 


	 
 


	Failure to Follow the Mechanics of the Loading Screen will be disqualified.
 


	 
 


	GM&#x2019;s will pick the best and valid entries from the submitted entries in Forum and will be posted in the Dark RO Page where people can react.
 


	 
 


	Popularity Contest scoring:
 


	1. 60% From Facebook Reacts
 


	2. 40% From GM Staff Choice (will be posting the top choices of each GM for transparency)
 


	
		
			20% Quality
		 
	
	
		
			10% Originality
		 
	
	
		
			10% Best Caption
		 
	



	 
 


	 
 


	Prizes:
 


	Top 1:  Winner will receive the exclusive Archangel Wings (Pick from the available 5 colors of the Archangel Wings; Brown, Purple, Black, Blue, Orange) + 100 Black Credits. Note that these wings will be included in the new GM box that we will release in the future. So there might be duplicates of the item in the future.
 


	 
 


	 
	 
 


	Top 2 and 3: Exclusive GM Box (R4-P17, Droideka, D-O Surprise Box and C-3PO) + 100 Black Credits.
 


	 
 


	 
 


	Consolation Prize:
 


	Participants whose artwork were posted in FB will receive 5x Black Credits.
 


	 
 


	Note: All submitted entries can be used by the Dark RO Rebirth Staff in the future for Loading Screen purposes ONLY, Use is valid until end of January 2021.</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jan 2021 12:15:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>New Year Countdown</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5754-new-year-countdown/?do=findComment&comment=31698]]></link><description>DarkRO Rebirth: New Year Countdown
 


	 
 


	Join us in greeting the New Year and welcoming the year of the Metal Ox! In line with the approaching Holiday, we will have a countdown event from December 23 to December 31 where we will give our faithful Dark RO players rewards each day. To receive the Countdown daily rewards, you will have to visit at prt_church 99 121 within the dates specified earlier.
 


	 
 


	The NPC will be available between 8pm - 8am Server Time (GMT +8). To continuously get the rewards, each player should visit the Countdown NPC daily without missing one single day (also you cannot skip days). Missing a day would result in disqualification from the whole event as you will not be able to receive future daily rewards and the Final Grand Prize at the end of the Countdown. 
 


	 
 


	There are no items required to get the rewards, but we would like to remind everyone to please ensure that there is space in your inventory for at least 10 new items. Items can be redeemed per MAC only and are account-bound (NON-TRADEABLE).This is a separate event from the daily rewards you have been receiving recently. 
 


	 
 


	The GMs will not provide information on the daily contents. Daily rewards will be a surprise. 
 


	 
 


	Thank you again for supporting Dark RO Rebirth! Happy Holidays!</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 03:04:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Santa's Hangout</title><link><![CDATA[https://dark-ro.com/forum/topic/5753-santas-hangout/?do=findComment&comment=31697]]></link><description>DarkRO Rebirth: Santa's Hangout
 


	It's the most wonderful time of the year!
 


	I hope you like the present of DarkRO: Rebirth from Santa's Hangout!
 


	As part of our Christmas Exclusive Event, we would like to give an experience exciting event for the incoming Holiday Season!
 


	 
 


	Santa's Objective: 
	Obtain Vintage Button and Freezing Snow Powder and trade it to Santa.
 


	 
 


	How to accumulate Vintage Button and Freezing Snow Powder:
 


	There would be (5) five farm sites to acquire:
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; xmas_dun01
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; xmas_dun02
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; xmas_fild01
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; ice_dun02
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; ice_dun03
 


	 
 


	Monsters to be killed:
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; Antonio
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; Marin
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; Christmas Cookie
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; Myst Case
 


	 
 


	&#x2022; Ice Titan
 


	 
 


	How to convert your Vintage Button and Freezing Snow Powder:
 


	 
 


	1. Talk to Santa at Lutie (xmas 117 157)
 


	 
 


	2. Conversion: 
 


	Trading 30x Freezing Snow Powder = Elves Box
 


	 
 


	Trading 20x Vintage Button = Christmas Box
 


	 
 


	Contents of Christmas Box:
 


	&#x2022; Santa Poring Hat
 


	&#x2022; Cat Santa Hat
 


	&#x2022; Louise Red Hat
 


	&#x2022; Antler Fedora
 


	&#x2022; Polar Bear Cap
 


	&#x2022; Yggdrasil Berry Box
 


	 &#x2022; Box of Thunder Box
 


	&#x2022; Poison Bottle Box
 


	&#x2022; Yggdrasil Seed Box 
 


	&#x2022; Aloevera Box
 


	 
 


	Contents of Elves Box:
 


	&#x2022; Yggdrasil Berry Box 
	 &#x2022; Box of Thunder Box
 


	&#x2022; Poison Bottle Box
 


	&#x2022; Yggdrasil Seed Box 
 


	&#x2022; Aloevera Box
 


	 
 


	Event Duration:
 


	December 23, 2020 - December 25, 2020 11:59PM GMT+08
 


	 
 


	"May your Christmas sparkle with moments of love, laugther and goodwill, and may the year ahead be full of contentment and joy together with DarkRO: Rebirth Community." 
	 
 


	Merry Christmas and Happy Holidays!</description><pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 02:55:33 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>